https://www.exquisitecrystals.com/privacy-policy-cookie-restriction-mode/

Compare Products
Have a Question? Ask Us.
Rose Quartz Geodes
QuartzAgateAmethystAmetrineAqua Aura QuartzAsbestos QuartzAurora QuartzBlue QuartzCarnelian AgateCathedral QuartzChlorite QuartzCitrine QuartzClear QuartzDream QuartzElestial QuartzEnhydro QuartzEtched QuartzFaden QuartzFenster QuartzFlame Aura QuartzGolden Healer QuartzGrowth Interference QuartzHematite with QuartzHerkimer DiamondIncluded QuartzJasperLaser QuartzLemurian Seed QuartzLightbrary QuartzLighting Strike QuartzLithium QuartzManifestation QuartzMetamorphosis QuartzNepal QuartzOpal Aura QuartzOther QuartzOuro Verde QuartzPetrified WoodPhantom QuartzPink Fire QuartzPrasioliteQue SeraRose QuartzRussian Lemurian QuartzRutilated QuartzScepter QuartzSmoky QuartzSpirit QuartzStrawberry QuartzSuper Seven QuartzTangerine QuartzTangerine Sun Aura QuartzTanzine Aura QuartzTibetan QuartzTourmaline in QuartzTrigonic QuartzMineralsAlexandriteAmazoniteAmberAmmoniteAngeliteApatiteApophylliteAquamarineAragoniteAstrophylliteAtlantisiteAzuriteBariteBoji StonesBytowniteCalciteCavansiteCelestiteCharoiteChalcopyriteChrysanthemum StoneChrysocollaChrysopraseCovelliteCreediteDanburiteDioptaseEmeraldEpidoteEudialyteFlintFluorcarletoniteFluoriteFuchsiteGarnetHaliteHematiteHemimorphiteHiddeniteInfiniteJadeJudy's JasperKunziteKyaniteLabradoriteLarimarLapisLepidoliteLibyan Desert GlassMalachiteMenaliteMoldaviteMoonstoneMorganiteNuummiteObsidianOpalOrpimentOthoclase Other MineralsPeridotPetalitePhenacitePietersitePrehnitePsilomelanePyriteRealgarRhodochrositeRhodoniteRosasiteRubySapphireScapoliteScoleciteSeleniteSeptarianSeraphiniteShungiteSmithsonsiteSpinelStaurolite - Fairy CrossStibniteStilbiteSugiliteSulfurSunstoneTanzaniteTektiteTiger EyeTiger IronTopazTourmalineTreasure AgateTremoliteTsavoriteTugtupiteTurquoiseVanadiniteVivianiteZinciteZirconTumbledTumbled StonesTumbled Stone SetsAccessoriesShapesBowlsCabochonsCarvingsHeartsEggsPendulumsPillow and Palm StonesShiva LinghamsSpheresTowersWandsWorry and Thumb StonesJewelryBeaded NecklacesBraceletsEarringsChakra JewelryChip NecklacesGemstone PendantsRussian Lemurian Ice Quartz JewelryTools For Evolution PendantsSundriesBooksIncenseLampsStands & AccessoriesOutletQuartz OutletMineral OutletCarvings & Shapes & Spheres OutletJewelry Outlet
About Us
Visit Our Gallery
You can visit our Gallery at Historic Fort Vancouver to see a selection of our best items. We feature many unique crystals and minerals.
Visit Us...
Company Info
Exquisite Crystals has been providing top quality specimens at great pricing on-line since 1999.
Your source for the crystal healer and crystal collector.
More About Us...
Our Products
We love crystals! Ethically sourced and hand selected, you'll be sure to get a gem when shopping at Exquisite Crystals.
Shop Now...
Home
Privacy and Cookie Policy
Privacy and Cookie Policy
This privacy policy sets out how this website (hereafter "ExquisiteCrystals.com LLC") uses and protects any information that you give the ExquisiteCrystals.com LLC while using this website. ExquisiteCrystals.com LLC is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. ExquisiteCrystals.com LLC may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
Name,
Contact information including email address,
Demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests,
Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers.
For the exhaustive list of cookies we collect see the List of cookies we collect section.
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
Order fulfillment.
Internal record keeping.
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email. We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Advertising
We use Google AdWords Remarketing to advertise ExquisiteCrystals.com LLC across the Internet, in particular on the Google Display Network. AdWords remarketing will display ads to you based on what parts of the ExquisiteCrystals.com LLC website you have viewed by placing a cookie on your web browser. This cookie does not in any way identify you or give access to your computer or mobile device. The cookie is used to indicate to other websites that "This person visited a particular page, so show them ads relating to that page." Google AdWords Remarketing allows us to tailor our marketing to better suit your needs and only display ads that are relevant to you.
If you do not wish to see ads from ExquisiteCrystals.com LLC you can opt out in several ways:
Opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting Google’s Ads Settings.
Opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
Whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by letting us know using our Contact Us information.
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please email us this request using our Contact Us information.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
List of cookies we collect
The table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store.
Cookie Name
Cookie Description
FORM_KEY
Stores randomly generated key used to prevent forged requests.
PHPSESSID
Your session ID on the server.
GUEST-VIEW
Allows guests to view and edit their orders.
PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART
A link to information about your cart and viewing history, if you have asked for this.
STF
Information on products you have emailed to friends.
STORE
The store view or language you have selected.
USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE
Indicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.
MAGE-CACHE-SESSID
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
MAGE-CACHE-STORAGE
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
MAGE-CACHE-STORAGE-SECTION-INVALIDATION
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
MAGE-CACHE-TIMEOUT
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
SECTION-DATA-IDS
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
PRIVATE_CONTENT_VERSION
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
X-MAGENTO-VARY
Facilitates caching of content on the server to make pages load faster.
MAGE-TRANSLATION-FILE-VERSION
Facilitates translation of content to other languages.
MAGE-TRANSLATION-STORAGE
Facilitates translation of content to other languages.
_gat_UA-403452-1
Set by Google Analytics, where the pattern element on the name contains the unique identity number of the account or website it relates to.
_gid
Used to store information of how visitors use a website.
NID
Used to a profile based on user's interest and display personalized ads to the user.
_ga
Store information anonymously and assigns a randomly generated number to identify unique visitors.
Updated August 1, 2019.
Copyright © 1999-2019 ExquisiteCrystals.com LLC. All rights reserved.
